<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:webfeeds="http://webfeeds.org/rss/1.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Owly's RSS Thoughts</title>
    <description>Hello there, well then, welcome to my RSS feed, oh my! This will be used as what I guess could be best called an "unsocial-social network". I'm unsure if anyone has ever done this before, that is where they use an RSS feed as just a blog, but that doesn't really matter.
	
	Follow for rubbish that fills my brain. Most of what I will post should be SFW, but I may use ruse language every now-and-then!
	</description>
    <webfeeds:logo>https://owlman.neocities.org/odds/dump/2020-06/floppy.png</webfeeds:logo>
    <webfeeds:accentColor>2b90d9</webfeeds:accentColor>
    <image>
      <url>https://owlman.neocities.org/odds/dump/2020-06/floppy.png</url>
      <title></title>
      <link></link>
    </image>
    <webfeeds:icon>https://owlman.neocities.org/odds/dump/2020-06/floppy.png</webfeeds:icon>
	<!-- <item> -->
      <!-- <title>TITLE</title> -->
      <!-- <pubDate>XXX, XX XX XXXX XX:XX:XX +0000</pubDate> -->
      <!-- <description> -->
	  
	  <!-- &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; -->
	  <!-- ~Owly -->
	  <!-- </description> -->
      <!-- <enclosure url="https://owlman.neocities.org/odds/dump/2020-06/" length="{:length=&gt;1194109}" type="image/png"/> -->
    <!-- </item> -->
	<item>
      <title>Test</title>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2020 05:05:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <description>
	  Hello there, this is a test!
	  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;
	  ~Owly
	  </description>
    </item>
	<item>
      <title>Francisco de Goya - Witches' Sabbath (1798)</title>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jun 2020 XX:XX:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <description>
	  "El Aquelarre", or as it is know in English rather than Spanish, "Witches' Sabbath" is a 1798 oil on canvas by Francisco Goya that is currently held in The Lázaro Galdiano Museum (Museo Lázaro Galdiano)
	  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;
	  The devil is seen here is the form of a garlanded goat, while a gathering of witches circle him. As can be seen on this oil on canvas painting, an older witch is holding infant in her hands.
	  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;
	  In this painting, the devil might be acting as an unholy priest at an initiation ceremony for the child, though popular superstition at the time believed the devil often fed on children, and human fetuses. The skeletons of two infants can be seen; one discarded to the left, the other held by a crone in the centre foreground.
	  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;
	  &lt;/br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
	  ~Owly
	  </description>
      <enclosure url="https://owlman.neocities.org/odds/dump/2020-06/witches_sabbath_1798.jpg" length="{:length=&gt;1194109}" type="image/png"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commission I Got!</title>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 May 2020 17:02:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <description>Hello there, everyone!
	  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;
	  A about a month ago I guess, my E-Friend, Randy of tehleroy.neocities.org made a post on his FA saying that he was going to do commissions, so as a way to support my friend (and to get something out of it), I did just that!  
	  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;
	  Here is what I got; me and my two dogs, Albert (left) and Rue (who was seen in my first RSS post). Thank you very much, Randy, and also make sure that you check out their other work.
	  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;
	  https://digipres.club/@OwlMan/104248229227769451
	  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;
	  ~Owly
	  </description>
      <enclosure url="https://owlman.neocities.org/odds/dump/2020-06/doggies.png" length="{:length=&gt;1194109}" type="image/png"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hello World!</title>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 May 2020 07:36:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <description>Why hello there, this is my first post, please enjoy a photo of one of my dogs, Rue!
	  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;
	  ~Owly</description>
      <enclosure url="https://owlman.neocities.org/odds/dump/2020-06/rue_20190811.jpg" length="{:length=&gt;1194109}" type="image/png"/>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>